...
.......
I see.
Yes, gentlemen.
Gentlemen.
May I have your attention, please?
Right now.
I'm asking everyone to draw a self-portrait.
Yes, sir.
You're doing a great job, aren't you?
But...
There's something I've been thinking about lately.
Illustrations...
You know, there are times when you have to draw
At such times
I've recently heard
that we are surprisingly good at drawing.
that we are good at drawing.
But I'm good at copying.
You're good at copying?
What do you do?
I'm better than Moe.
Cool!
I'm good at it.
I'm good at drawing in my own way.
In your own way.
It's your own way.
It's the most original thing you can do.
It's not a compliment.
It's...
I don't...
.......
I still think...
I still like this picture.
I like drawing.
I like to draw a lot of things.
I want to show you that I'm on a different level.
Then...
Hana's paintings are the best.
I'm the best at drawing?
That's not what this is about.
That's right.
Will you do that?
Glasses.
Then show us the real Hana.
Here's my self-portrait.
There you go.
What is a self-portrait?
Did you learn self-portrait from your teacher?
You're good at it.
It's very good. It's called a flower painting.
It's easy to tell.
Of course it's really good.
And she's cute.
It's not a self-portrait.
It's an illustration.
Illustration.
Look, compare... face sideways.
It's too beautiful.
It's totally over-glorified.
It's not a self-portrait.
Come on, it's just a drawing.
It's a self-portrait.
It's art.
This is how I see myself.
No, it's not.
That's why I think it fits.
Oh.
It looks good.
Okay, let's all see it together.
Stop complaining about Wada.
He's talking so much about Ilan and stuff.
I've already done this.
Self-portrait.
This one's cuter.
You say the most amazing things.
That's what's so cute about you.
I'm good at self-portraits.
I think I'm pretty good at drawing people realistically.
Here's a self-portrait.
I'm going to compare them.
Because you know what?
I have to work really hard
I have to work really hard.
I draw my face too much.
I can only draw in illustration.
It's not good at all.
It's just like you.
That's me!
Art is easy.
Artistically.
I'm good at it.
I draw moles and stuff.
They're from a horror movie.
But maybe I painted them a little too pretty.
No.
It's cute.
Let's see... you'll love it.
Ta-da!
Which one?
It's not a self-portrait, and it's not an illustration.
Oh, my God.
First of all, her hair is different lengths.
But...
I wanted to do the lip pouting, but I messed up.
The mountain of lips.
Close your mouth.
Ah, this mountain part
I wanted to draw a mountain
I drew it one more time.
And Modoka-chan said she was able to draw this.
Modoka-chan, you had another candidate, didn't you?
I had another candidate, right?
I'd like to do either one, though.
The other one is
this one
Same.
Not even close.
There's no neck.
I wonder if his neck has always been up.
I wonder if his neck was up the whole time.
I wonder if his neck's been up this whole time.
It's just like him. It's just like him.
Like, like, like, like.
Well, just like that...
I had a self-portrait painted.
It's not like I'm a good singer today.
It's not about singing well today.
It's about drawing with the eyes of the heart.
It's about how
How I always look at the members
I want to measure
I'd like to measure your drawing ability.
I don't look at
I draw without looking at the sketchbook
I draw without looking at it.
What are you going to do?
I'll make mistakes.
I don't think so.
There, there, there, there.
Right there, right there.
Notice the sound.
It's okay.
That's all right.
I'm going to ask you to hold it and draw a square like this.
I'm going to ask you to draw a square while holding it like this.
Look at the members.
Don't look at yourself.
Always look at the members of your heart.
If you look at them all the time
I think you will be able to draw well.
I'm sure you can do it.
You might want to let me look at your sketchbook.
It's a project.
I might want you to do it.
Oh, sorry.
Sorry.
Sorry. Sorry.
Championship to be drawn on the third
Applause
5 more!
Three.
The End
This is for real.
Voila.
Wow.
It's so bad.
So bad.